hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski on this podcast we
talk about ways for you to grow in your
life and your business to get more
results now this week I'm going to be
talking about something that I think
affects everybody that I meet in
business and it's something I think you
can really apply and get a lot of value
out of
I feel that I have talked about this a
lot before I've shared this a lot before
by the way I got a little Halston here
in my hands
uh mom's out of the store and if I sit
him down he's not too happy so I'm just
going to hold him and we're going to
talk to the camera and we're gonna do
the podcast together
say hi Halston what's up buddy
anyways so the biggest thing that a lot
of people get wrong in their business is
there's so much that we're told about
how to do things the right way what's
the right way to do things what's the
best way to do things what's the best
practices and I see so many people
concerning themselves with this of doing
everything the right way doing
everything following through with things
the right way and of course like they're
thinking well I don't want to do
anything the wrong way right obviously
we don't want to do things the wrong way
in our business
but that inordinate focus on always
figuring out doing things the right way
and not doing something or stagnating or
stopping ourselves from actually doing
something until it's the right way for
instance here's a great example
the right way to create a podcast quote
unquote is in a studio not holding a
nine month old in the middle of your
living room with boxes because you just
moved into a new house but guess what
here I am today because this is the
moment in time that I found 20 30
minutes to record a podcast today and
and and and that's how I have made so
much money in business that's how my mom
has made so much money in business
that's how the people that I work with
that make the maximum amount of money in
their business do so is they don't wait
until the best practices Right Way Comes
Along they don't sit around waiting
until success aligns and their stars and
their lucky stars align and they do
everything perfect they take action
imperfectly and imperfect action might
look like literally recording a podcast
with a baby on your hip while you're
doing that some of y'all might like not
even think that you could do that and so
I want to just encourage you of that and
I mean I'm literally using this as an
active example for you of how you could
be making more money in your business
and you might be sacrificing
success in your business and in your
life
by trying to do everything the right way
according to what somebody else has told
you you know I have people they come to
me all the time they're like What's the
right price to charge in my business
what's the right software to use
what's the right platform to use
and you could use any number of
different platforms now I get that and I
have recommendations for different
platforms that are easier to set up
easier to build on easier to get results
with
but there's no such thing as a quote
unquote right way one way of doing
everything I think that's one of the
biggest fallacies that people have when
it comes to business is that there is a
single path to success there's a
singular right way to build everything
and if you don't do it that one right
way then you can't be successful that's
not been a reality in my career and I've
worked for two decades with
multi-multi-millionaire business owners
myself I built my own business to over a
million dollars in the last year we've
made Seven figures in our business
and yeah little Halston he's he's
falling asleep here while I'm talking
I feel like he would fall asleep while I
did this which is great and so
understand
that if you're always always trying to
do everything the right way in your
business
you're going to suffer
you're going to actually experience
failure
the pursuit of
the most right way of doing things in
your business
is the cause and effect
behind much of the reasons why you might
not be making the kind of money you want
to make
why you might not have the kind of
success that you want
because you're waiting until you come
across the right way instead of
doing things
with what you have in front of me I have
people ask me right now well Jeremiah
like you could build your business with
XYZ software that's better than what
you're doing why haven't you moved it
over to everything and and and and and
there are superior ways that I could
build my business
and I intentionally choose to not build
them the way that I should do according
to what everybody tells me because I
would rather just go make a ton of money
doing things the way that I can
consistently do the way that I started
them instead of getting off track
distracting myself to quote unquote
align with some version of what the
right way is and actions that I quote
unquote should do According to some
arbitrarily
decided version of should do in business
that people come up with and by the way
that's all that any of the right way
that people say is
I mean you could make that argument even
to what I'm saying right here but this
is why I particularly speak to coaches
mentors trainers because we're not
we're not heart surgeons
we're not building automobiles we're not
building houses okay
I just bought a new house like there's a
there's a construction
standard that you want a house to
measure up to and this house was built
in the 90s it's solid as a rock it's a
brick house I mean it's it's amazing
it's it's it's a it's it's stood the
test of time and so they built it the
right way there was a standard to do
that in the mentoring and coaching
business there are some
best practices when it comes to getting
leads and there's a better way to do
things uh but what I find is people that
are not making money in the beginning
they are inordinately focused on the
quote-unquote right way best way and are
almost I and I hear it because I hear
them in my coaching group they actually
tell me this I've had people actually
verbalize and say this to me I can't
build my business until I know XYZ oh
and then they'll say I am crying and
shuddering inside emotionally
destroyed because I can't figure out
what the right way is to do x y z
and so that barrier that is created
by
I need things to be the right way I need
them to be perfect
It ultimately comes from believing that
if things were the right way then
success would happen
and if they're not the right way success
won't happen
and that belief is false when it comes
to the coaching and mentoring business
that there's a quote unquote right way
to do things there's no single right way
to do anything in this business if
you're learning from me in my podcast I
will tell you if there's a like a path
to take or things like that but I see
this particularly when it comes to the
software packages that people are using
when it comes particularly to the
like initial getting off the ground
their domain name their wet like
and and and there's so many resources
out there now in 2023 2024 and Beyond
in the world that we're living in to
streamline and simplify things
that there's actually a lot of Right Way
best practices and even companies out
there that provide those I tell people
this YouTube
chat GPT
Google
and then Facebook groups those are four
incredible resources if you're ever
stuck and you don't know how to do
something
even if it's legal stuff even if it's
website stuff even if it's it's
marketing stuff even if it's like how to
take payment stuff things like that
you can learn it and you can even ask
chat gbt like how to do this you can get
help you don't need to be stuck if
you're a part of my mentorship program
you can get help
you can ask me questions to help you
there's no reason to be stuck but the
biggest reason that I see people not
making money in their business is an
inordinate focus on doing things and
getting started the quote unquote right
way and being
so avoidant of anything that might not
have the cha-ching stamp of approval a
hundred percent guaranteed this is the
bona fide right way to do it when in
fact
what actually produces results in this
business financially is not going to
have that stamp of approval on it most
of the time because it's Cutting Edge
most of the time because in the
mentorship business when it actually
comes to promoting and building your
your your your your brand and actually
getting clients and actually getting
people to become a client of yours
you're not going to run into those
things at all you're not going to have
the quote unquote cha-ching bona fide
certified
one way to do things
and that's also how people can get
um LED astray
it's also how people can lose a lot of
money it's also how actually how I see a
lot of people
losing in their business is they're
searching for and looking for a single
one best practice right way to do
everything
and it was it's literally what stops
people from experiencing success
is this need for things to be perfect
how they should to have Clarity
certainty certification bona fide
knowing exactly what the best right most
certain thing to do is when in fact that
does not exist in reality
at all
ever
for any successful business owner that I
know
period
what they do is they take the resources
they take the knowledge they take the
people they have and they make the best
by basically Jerry rigging their
resources together in the best way they
can
that's the right way to do things that's
actually the path to financial success
and so if you're hearing me right now
and you're like man I just can never do
that challenge that thinking if you want
to be a millionaire if you want to be
successful challenge that thinking
where did that come from
whoever told you that you need to make
sure that things are perfect in order to
be successful and to not do things as
people say this they say I would rather
not start at all
than possibly start the wrong way
and it's like it just I have no gauge
for that personally because I just know
that that's so divorced from even coming
close to financial success
but when you can learn to bootstrap it
to get kind of Scrappy with it to figure
it out to make the best of the resources
you have
that's where cash flow starts coming in
that's where you actually making the
kind of money that you want to make in
your business actually starts to come
together and the people that I know that
are successful they didn't wait until
they knew things were perfect they
figured it out as they went along they
made the best of the resources they had
even if they weren't the quote unquote
perfect best they went out there they
continued to to test things out to
experiment to see how was it going to
work out and they were willing
to bend the rules to break the rules to
not
try to find and color inside the lines
they actually realized that financial
success comes from coloring Outside the
Lines
and that's what I want to encourage you
in today like if you're watching this
right now
if you're watching this right now and
you want to create financial success for
you and your family
you have to realize
that waiting until everything's perfect
is not how that's going to happen
waiting until quote unquote the stars
align and you feel certain you will not
feel certain
in your business to the point that you
know that things are right ever and
that's a facade
the people that I know are that are most
successful they have an Ever
experimentation mindset they're not
looking for that moment of Peace inside
their heart to know that things are
ready to move forward with
to know that things are ready to finally
pull the trigger on I got peace around
this so now I'm going to pull the
trigger like that's that's not how
success is created that's how failures
are made that's how continuous failure
is made and and when you've done that
enough times by the way I'm speaking to
you as somebody that has done a hundred
percent of everything that I'm telling
you
to not do
because that's how I live my life
because that's how I was trained because
that's how I was taught
that's how I was even raised
which is funny
because I was raised by a mother who
didn't do that but she taught me to do
that for my own safety to protect me as
a mother
trying to protect her kids
she told me to do things different than
how she even did them
herself for my own protection and safety
and now she commends me to this day we
have conversations mom and son as two
business owners of the fact that I went
against what she taught me and raised me
to do for my own safety and that I've
actually broken through to financial
success by going against how I was
raised literally
I plan on instilling in my son to be
Fearless
to not
be afraid to go out there to not be
afraid to experiment to of course be
cautious about certain things in this
business
you don't have like like you're not
going to have a benefit from being
overly cautious
there's not a benefit from tiptoeing and
walking around on eggshells being
concerned and worried that things aren't
perfect that they might not work out
that they might not go the right way
that's actually the formula for
financial
failure
in this business model
of coaching mentoring training being a
thought leader
and so if you want to be successful it's
going to take doing some hard scary
risky things it's going to take putting
yourself out there without guarantees
without knowing how something's going to
turn out just to see what happens
and that's what produces success and
you're not always going to have the
quote unquote right way of it being set
up
but consistently having momentum
produces results momentum beats the
perfect funnel the perfect system the
perfect software every day of the week
100 of the time and again that's coming
from somebody who is obsessive
compulsive literally around the perfect
funnel the perfect strategy putting
everything perfect I was obsessed with
perfectionism for the longest time when
I set out to build my own business it
bit me in the butt and that's why I
struggled to make the kind of money that
we're making today in the beginning when
I set out there to do it myself I had
all the strategies but I was overly
concerned with perfection
and that stopped me from making the kind
of money that I wanted to make and as
soon as I shifted into what I'm telling
you right now in this podcast that's
when the finances started to come in
that's what changed my life forever
and it'll change yours as well listen
I encourage you take this to Heart Take
it serious and apply it in your life
listen if this podcast has helped you
share it with somebody don't hold it
back to yourself don't keep it to
yourself share it with somebody else
that's out there pass it on as well join
us for one of our live events that we're
doing we host free business training
events where I teach you and and give
you the strategies of what's working in
your business free of charge
and I'm not just talking about like
these are not marketing like cleverly
disguised marketing pitches these are
actual events where I give you the
secret sauce or I pull back the curtain
and show you what it takes to be
successful
make sure to join us for some of those
in the future grow your life and we'll
talk soon have a good one
[Music]
foreign